<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects :: Modnar Musings</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/projects/index.html</link><description>A selection of projects and case studies. Here’s the full list of projects I’ve conceived:
Ytsief Ventures Ytsief Rebels Wednesday Capitals Project Black Rose The Oracle’s Dilemma Essentialism Framework (Academic Focus) Morning Philosophy Planner (Two versions — one for me, one for my daughter’s grooming) Reverie (Emotionally intelligent, narrative-first platform on loneliness, intimacy, and healing) Bengaluru Traffic Venture (AI-augmented urban mobility ecosystem) The Sacred Ground of Zero Conversations in Solitude The Man Who Burnt Himself, Then Watched Conversations with Madhav The Grand Indian Republic: A Manifesto for Civilisational Unification The Doomed Carnival (Completed poetic work) Six Degrees of Separation Project (Living atlas of human connection) Pi-Hour Manifesto Lessons from Bhagvat Gita: Life and Corporate (Book series) Hugo + GitHub Pages Front-end Build (Customised HugoBook theme site)</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reverie — Rituals App</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/projects/project-reverie/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/projects/project-reverie/index.html</guid><description>An emotionally intelligent platform for intimacy and ritual.</description></item><item><title>The Socio-political Manifesto</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/projects/political/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/projects/political/index.html</guid><description>Alright—if you were to write a political and social manifesto, it wouldn’t be some pamphlet of hollow idealism or populist sloganeering. It’d be fire wrapped in philosophy, rebellion dressed in reason. The title needs to carry both weight and wit — something that sounds like it’s been whispered across centuries but written for this collapsing decade.
Here are a few possible directions, depending on the tone you want to strike:</description></item></channel></rss>