<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Conversations with Madhav :: Modnar Musings</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/index.html</link><description>‘Conversations with Madhav’ is a series of poetic monologues, dialogues, and reflections where the narrator confronts God, absence, memory, morality, and madness. It is both prayer and profanity — a sacred theatre of questions that refuse to die.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Madhav: A Pragmatic and Profane Profile</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/00_madhav/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/00_madhav/index.html</guid><description>Madhav is the contradiction that sustains consciousness — the divine intelligence that mocks devotion, the silence that dismantles prayer. He is not to be worshipped, only to be recognised.</description></item><item><title>The Narrator: Anatomy of the Confessor</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/01_narrator/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/01_narrator/index.html</guid><description>An unflinching profile of the narrator in 'Conversations with Madhav' — the human voice that argues with silence, smokes with God, and keeps speaking after meaning has died.</description></item><item><title>Madhav and the Narrator: The Duality of Dialogue</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/01a_duality/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/01a_duality/index.html</guid><description>An extended essay exploring the metaphysical and psychological duality of Madhav and the Narrator in 'Conversations with Madhav' — a study of divine silence, human defiance, and the meaning of dialogue after belief.</description></item><item><title>The Doctrine of Smoke</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/01b_doctine/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/01b_doctine/index.html</guid><description>The Doctrine of Smoke is the sacred logic of the Madhav Mythos — an existential scripture that treats smoke as symbol, language, ritual, and philosophy. It redefines faith through the act of burning.</description></item><item><title>The Liturgy of Ash</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/01c_lithurgy/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/01c_lithurgy/index.html</guid><description>A meditative and metaphysical exploration of ash as symbol, theology, and psychological state. The Liturgy of Ash completes the triad of Fire, Smoke, and Ash — the divine cycle of awareness in Conversations with Madhav.</description></item><item><title>The Silence of Embers</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/01d_embers/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/01d_embers/index.html</guid><description>The final doctrine in the combustion cycle — Fire, Smoke, and Ash as the sacred loop of creation, transformation, and rest. Embers are the whisper between endings and beginnings, where divinity and consciousness merge.</description></item><item><title>And The Man Smoked</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/02_smoked/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:14:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/conversations/02_smoked/index.html</guid><description>And The Man Smoked Prologue Madhav sat across from me — uninvited, as always — in that quiet hour when the world feels like it’s running out of breath. He didn’t speak. He just watched, eyes glimmering with that infuriating mix of knowing and indifference. I broke the silence the only way I knew how.
With smoke.
Monologue And the man smoked.
Not for pleasure. Not for pain. But because silence demanded punctuation. The world had grown too loud, too insistent — and smoke was the only language left that didn’t need translation.</description></item></channel></rss>