<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ventures on Modnar Musings</title><link>/posts/ventures/</link><description>Recent content in Ventures on Modnar Musings</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/ventures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Venture + Blog [Philosophy]</title><link>/posts/ventures/venture-+-blog-philosophy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/ventures/venture-+-blog-philosophy/</guid><description>&lt;style&gt; @import "https://enemyatgates.github.io/hosting/CG%2BJOPLINSTYLEUSER_%7B00%7D.css" &lt;/style&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduction to Philosophical Concepts&lt;/strong&gt;: Create introductory posts on fundamental philosophical concepts like ethics, metaphysics, epistemology, and aesthetics. Explain them in simple terms for readers new to philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Philosophy and Pop Culture&lt;/strong&gt;: Explore how philosophical ideas are depicted in movies, books, and TV shows. Analyze the deeper philosophical themes in popular culture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Philosophical Debates&lt;/strong&gt;: Write about ongoing or classic philosophical debates. For example, explore the free will vs. determinism debate, the mind-body problem, or the trolley problem.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Venture + Brand "Thorian"</title><link>/posts/ventures/venture-+-brand-_thorian_/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/ventures/venture-+-brand-_thorian_/</guid><description>&lt;style&gt; @import "https://enemyatgates.github.io/hosting/CG%2BJOPLINSTYLEUSER_%7B00%7D.css" &lt;/style&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2025.04.21 @ 19:49:00 IST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="venture--brand-thorian"&gt;Venture + Brand &amp;ldquo;Thorian&amp;rdquo;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#venture--brand-thorian"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="branding"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Branding&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#branding"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brand &amp;ldquo;Thorian&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brand &amp;ldquo;Xandra&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="ventures"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ventures&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#ventures"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Corporate Trainer Profile: Brochure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate thirteen business plans which incorporates the functions of Marketing, Data Science, and Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create an elaborate business plan for a Dating, Extra Marital Affairs, and Sugar Daddy Business in India.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="projects"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#projects"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorian on Life akin to Cunk on Life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am Thorian!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Black-Paper Blueprint: India&amp;rsquo;s World Dominance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write a Book&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="profiles-based-on-"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Profiles&lt;/strong&gt; based on &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;the man who knows nothing&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;a class="anchor" href="#profiles-based-on-"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorian, Vikas Chandra&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorian, Xander Amgine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorian, Xandra Amgine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="erotica"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Erotica&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#erotica"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The protagonist (a young woman) meets an her older neighbour for the first time who subsequently enamours, dominates and manipulates her into a purely sexual relationship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="articles-for-the-newsletters--on-the-following"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Articles&lt;/strong&gt; for the newsletters &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Modnar Musings&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Unleashed Utterances&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; on the following:&lt;a class="anchor" href="#articles-for-the-newsletters--on-the-following"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Curiosity meets Creativity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Arm Yourself because No One else will Save you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reconnecting with the Lost Connections&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Anatomy of the Middle Class from the perspective of its nature as apologetic, cursed, and trapped.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The prudes have destroyed the society rather than the degenerates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All I want is to discuss philosophy with a woman adorning a bikini alongside a pool while sipping on whiskey during twilight whilst smoking cigars.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be aware and beware that today is Friday the Thirteenth, don&amp;rsquo;t venture out of your safe heavens, the devil is waiting for you out there to drag you to hell, and torture you for eternity, strangulate your spirit, destroy your soul.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The path of excess leads to the tower of wisdom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The experience of survival is the key to gravity of love.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find the one who&amp;rsquo;ll guide you to the limits of your choice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are prisoners to our own desires.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Music is the epitome of our lives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are hardwired to self-destruct.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disruption from a strategic and creative perspective.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life of full disclosure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gandhi-an Philosophies in the Modern World.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marketing: The Black Box Theory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Artificial Intelligence: History and Future.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Woke Liberal Analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is an Addiction wort a Life?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is Life worth an Addiction?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Depression, Drugs, and Suicide.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thinking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership and Thinking isn&amp;rsquo;t about seeking answers but is about seeking questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The best use case of Artificial Intelligence lies in seeking questions rather than seeking answers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The essence of Artificial Intelligence lies in seeking questions instead of seeking answers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One must walk with conviction to a certain death.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life is finicky and fragile while being incidental and coincidence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A man must knock on thousand doors before expecting a response.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s an underlying charm in the eyes of a woman staring at you, as if her gaze holds a thousand unspoken words, a silent conversation that lingers between curiosity and understanding.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working in pornography can be a liberating experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love is ephemeral and ethereal.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A man must confront death and die a zillion times before he is bestowed with immortality and attains nirvana.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feed the absurdities into Artificial Intelligence models, and everything crashes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pushing Boundaries with Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Core of Artificial Intelligence is nothing but Regurgitation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The True Test of Intelligence is in handling of the Absurd and the Obscure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A few mistakes must be committed by ourselves instead of wholly learning from the mistakes of the others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mistakes: A Dichotomy of Life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transformation from the perspective of personal, community, social, collective, business etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every action and statement of ours has either a political or religious or sexual ramification.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Myth of Neutrality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone has a WhatsApp Uncle, if you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, then they have one. Everyone has a crazy neighbour, if you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, then they have one. Everyone has an idiot batch-mate, if you don&amp;rsquo;t have one, then they have one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We all are prostitutes, some are mentally prostituting, some are emotionally prostituting, some are physically prostituting, some are commercially prostituting, and some needs to prostitute on combination, to satiate their lives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My whole life has been akin to an untethered kite dancing in a hurricane. Always fluttering, always struggling, and never settling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every relationship is transactional. That&amp;rsquo;s the beauty or ugliness of it; whichever way you see it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The only traits a man need is to endure and survive, and that&amp;rsquo;s for leaders as well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My conundrum is about whether to work-out the path of the fate or to work-out the fate of the path.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I feel safe, I feel scared, I feel ready, and yet unprepared.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The cosmos has thrown a curveball at me, and I am planning to hit out of the spectrum.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A country whose pathways viz. the footpaths, the pavements, the the village roads, the city roads, the highways, the express-ways, and the interstates are interlaced with garbage, potholes, blockades, barricades, processions, speed-breakers, and nubile-drivers can never be on the path to development, progress, future, and global-superpower.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be ready to burn yourself in your own flame; how could you rise anew if you have not first become ashes?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When a man confines himself to a room, the world has only three people &amp;ldquo;I, me, and myself.&amp;rdquo; Existence becomes a curse, survival a sentence, and mind a prison. Though, it can be a beauty in solitude, divine in distress, nirvana in reflections, and moksha in abyss.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You ever wonder if the devil&amp;rsquo;s just a man who survived too long?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conjure up a deadbeat fallout style philosophical monologue (lengthy one) based on the song &amp;ldquo;Gangsta&amp;rsquo;s Paradise&amp;rdquo; by Coolio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every night I ponder over my fate, was I destined to be here, &amp;ldquo;an obscure existence in an obscure hamlet.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every night I ponder over my fate—was I destined to be here? An obscure existence, in an obscure hamlet, forgotten by time and untouched by mercy. The stars above don&amp;rsquo;t speak anymore… they just stare, cold and indifferent, as if they too have given up on the story of me.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every damn night I lie awake, chewing on the same thought—was this always gonna be it? Me. Stuck in this rotting patch of nowhere. Some forgotten speck where even the wind sounds bored. No glory. No purpose. Just silence thick enough to choke on and memories that hit like shrapnel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Someone on the edge and perhaps a ledge.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every night I crawl back into my head, and it asks the same question—is this it? Was I born just to rot in this piss-stained corner of the world? Some godforsaken hamlet no one maps, where even the crows look lost. I talk to shadows now. At least they listen. The wind keeps whispering things I&amp;rsquo;m starting to believe. And the ledge&amp;hellip; the ledge don&amp;rsquo;t judge. It just waits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In a world where everyone is clamouring to be the lion, the tiger, the eagle, the falcon, the wolf—symbols of dominance, aggression, grandeur, and control—where does the Kabootar fit in? The Kabootar Manifesto; The Kabootar Philosophy; The Kabootar Ideology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Old Man, the Dog, and the Stick Parable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In a nation stifled by the language row, silence didn&amp;rsquo;t remain golden—it turned militant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Where tongues were once celebrated, now silence is enforced. And they call it unity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With the language row stifling India, apparently, &amp;ldquo;silence is golden&amp;rdquo; become vehement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Burn the play-book and bring back the profanities in our conversation, especially the business conversations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In an era of global dominance and warfare, India must dump the fucking play-book of the international relations to achieve her vision of being a global superpower.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Life is nothing but a relentless pursuit of endurance and survival, while carving out a path for yourself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="miscellaneous"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miscellaneous&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#miscellaneous"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Has created a manifesto titled &amp;ldquo;The Manifesto of the Self-Governed Daughter,&amp;rdquo; written in the voice of Xandra Amgine Thorian. It is structured into 16 chapters, each divided into sections and sub-sections, intended to be a 100-page document focusing on self-governance, power, identity, and strategic transformation for their daughter. Each chapter has symbolic themes and philosophical undertones, replacing the earlier plan for sixteen letters.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Venture + E-Recycle</title><link>/posts/ventures/venture-+-e-recycle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/ventures/venture-+-e-recycle/</guid><description>&lt;style&gt; @import "https://enemyatgates.github.io/hosting/CG%2BJOPLINSTYLEUSER_%7B00%7D.css" &lt;/style&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2025.04.02 @ 21:25:00 IST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="venture--e-recycle"&gt;Venture + E-Recycle&lt;a class="anchor" href="#venture--e-recycle"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;${toc}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sure, here&amp;rsquo;s an idea for a start-up:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Name&lt;/strong&gt;: EcoTechRecycle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Idea&lt;/strong&gt;: EcoTechRecycle is a start-up that focuses on providing sustainable solutions for electronic waste management. The company&amp;rsquo;s core mission is to reduce the environmental impact of discarded electronics while promoting a circular economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Features&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;E-Waste Collection and Recycling&lt;/strong&gt;: EcoTechRecycle sets up collection centers in various communities and partners with businesses to collect and recycle electronic waste such as old smartphones, laptops, tablets, and other gadgets. They ensure that these electronic devices are properly recycled, preventing harmful materials from ending up in landfills.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Venture + Entrepreneurial</title><link>/posts/ventures/venture-+-entrepreneurial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/ventures/venture-+-entrepreneurial/</guid><description>&lt;style&gt; @import "https://enemyatgates.github.io/hosting/CG%2BJOPLINSTYLEUSER_%7B00%7D.css" &lt;/style&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2023.04.01 00:00:00 IST&lt;/strong&gt;: Created
&lt;strong&gt;2025.03.02 02:13:00 IST&lt;/strong&gt;: Updated&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id="venture--entrepreneurial"&gt;Venture + Entrepreneurial&lt;a class="anchor" href="#venture--entrepreneurial"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;${toc}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="ytsief-ventures-private-limited"&gt;Ytsief Ventures Private Limited&lt;a class="anchor" href="#ytsief-ventures-private-limited"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Umbrella Venture, partners and directors:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorian, Vikas Chandra&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorian, Kalpana Dubhal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thorian, Shubhi Ved Ytsief&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="ytsief-analytics-private-limited"&gt;Ytsief Analytics Private Limited&lt;a class="anchor" href="#ytsief-analytics-private-limited"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marketing and Data Science Company:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design Logo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design Website and Color Palette&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio Pitch Content and Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio Video Content and Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Social Media Marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search Engine Optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="ytsief-creatives-private-limited"&gt;Ytsief Creatives Private Limited&lt;a class="anchor" href="#ytsief-creatives-private-limited"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Entertainment Company
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Music (Electronic) and Music Videos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Music Events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talent Hunt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Influencers Launch and Promotion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Celebrity Endorsements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="wednesday-capitals-private-limited"&gt;Wednesday Capitals Private Limited&lt;a class="anchor" href="#wednesday-capitals-private-limited"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An Investment and Trading Company:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Portfolio Management Services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equity Advisory, Trading and Investments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Derivatives Advisory and Trading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mutual Fund Advisory and Investments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Real Estate Advisory and Investments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="political-aspirations"&gt;Political Aspirations&lt;a class="anchor" href="#political-aspirations"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Indian National Congress or Independent
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Year 2023, Application to Indian National Congress for its revival and reengineering.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Year 2023, Membership Indian National Congress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Year 2029, Member of Parliament Candidature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Year 2034, Member of Parliament Candidature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Year 2039, Member of Parliament Candidature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Year 2044, Member of Parliament Candidature and Cabinet Minister Candidature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Year 2049, Member of Parliament Candidature and Prime Minister Candidature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="../../seton/Ventures/Venture%20&amp;#43;%20Blog%20[Philosophy].md"&gt;Venture + Blog [Philosophy]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Venture + Nyxathrone</title><link>/posts/ventures/venture-+-nyxathrone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/ventures/venture-+-nyxathrone/</guid><description>&lt;style&gt; @import "https://enemyatgates.github.io/hosting/CG%2BJOPLINSTYLEUSER_%7B00%7D.css" &lt;/style&gt;
&lt;h1 id="-"&gt;🧭 &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Project Nyxathrone&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id="-target-to-be-the-prime-minister-of-india-age-4550"&gt;&lt;em&gt;🎯 Target: To be the Prime Minister of India&lt;/em&gt; [Age 45–50]&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-target-to-be-the-prime-minister-of-india-age-4550"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="--age-1618"&gt;🔹 &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Foundations of Fire&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; [Age 16–18]&lt;a class="anchor" href="#--age-1618"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id="--age-1822"&gt;🔹 &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Mind of Steel&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; [Age 18–22]&lt;a class="anchor" href="#--age-1822"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id="--age-2226"&gt;🔹 &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Boots on the Ground&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; [Age 22–26]&lt;a class="anchor" href="#--age-2226"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id="--age-2631"&gt;🔹 &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Fighter Emerges&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; [Age 26–31]&lt;a class="anchor" href="#--age-2631"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id="--age-3136"&gt;🔹 &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;The National Firepower&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; [Age 31–36]&lt;a class="anchor" href="#--age-3136"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id="--age-3641"&gt;🔹 &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Queen-maker Phase&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; [Age 36–41]&lt;a class="anchor" href="#--age-3641"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id="--age-4145"&gt;🔹 &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Leap to the Prime Minister&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; [Age 41–45]&lt;a class="anchor" href="#--age-4145"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id="--age-1645"&gt;🔹 &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ongoing Skills Checklist&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; [Age 16–45]&lt;a class="anchor" href="#--age-1645"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id="--1"&gt;🔹 &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Final Line&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#--1"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div style="page-break-after: always;"&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h1 id="--age-1618-1"&gt;🔹 &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Foundations of Fire&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; [Age 16–18]&lt;a class="anchor" href="#--age-1618-1"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3 id="-high-school-focus"&gt;✅ High School Focus&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-high-school-focus"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;mdash; Humanities with History, Political Science, Economics, Philosophy, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Venture + Political Manifesto</title><link>/posts/ventures/venture-+-political-manifesto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/ventures/venture-+-political-manifesto/</guid><description>&lt;style&gt; @import "https://enemyatgates.github.io/hosting/CG%2BJOPLINSTYLEUSER_%7B00%7D.css" &lt;/style&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2025.04.02 @ 21:26:00 IST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="venture--political-manifesto"&gt;Venture + Political Manifesto&lt;a class="anchor" href="#venture--political-manifesto"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;${toc}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="manifesto-of-the-oppressed-a-call-for-socialist-revolution"&gt;Manifesto of the Oppressed: A Call for Socialist Revolution&lt;a class="anchor" href="#manifesto-of-the-oppressed-a-call-for-socialist-revolution"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comrades, workers, tillers of the soil, the exploited of all stripes!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For too long, we have suffered under the crushing weight of a rigged system. The capitalist machine grinds on, churning out profit for the privileged few while leaving the vast majority to toil for scraps. We are the bakers with empty cupboards, the builders sleeping in the streets, the minds overflowing with potential chained to dead-end jobs.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Venture + Politics [Indian National Congress]</title><link>/posts/ventures/venture-+-politics-indian-national-congress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/ventures/venture-+-politics-indian-national-congress/</guid><description>&lt;style&gt; @import "https://enemyatgates.github.io/hosting/CG%2BJOPLINSTYLEUSER_%7B00%7D.css" &lt;/style&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2023.04.01 01:05:00&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Mr. Rahul Gandhi,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;History and Legacy&lt;/strong&gt;
- India
- Congress / Indian National Congress
&lt;strong&gt;Background&lt;/strong&gt;
India&amp;rsquo;s democracy is on a dangerous path and it&amp;rsquo;s on the verge of collapsing, if nothing is done on an immediate basis and in a concrete manner. As a responsible citizen of India, like yourself, I am of the strong view that the onus of resurrecting the Indian Democracy lies on every citizen, including me. In this time of critical juncture in India&amp;rsquo;s past, present and future, it&amp;rsquo;s high time we come together and formulate a formidable strategy, and put it in action.
&lt;strong&gt;Who am I?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;What I stand for?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;What I aspire for?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;What I can contribute?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;What we shall do?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;
- Vision and Objectives
- Campaign(s)
- Initiatives
- Plan
- Execution
&lt;strong&gt;Action Plan&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Roles and Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Media Enrollment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Venture + Projects</title><link>/posts/ventures/venture-+-projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/ventures/venture-+-projects/</guid><description>&lt;style&gt; @import "https://enemyatgates.github.io/hosting/CG%2BJOPLINSTYLEUSER_%7B00%7D.css" &lt;/style&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2025.04.26 @ 00:07:00 IST&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="venture--projects"&gt;Venture + Projects&lt;a class="anchor" href="#venture--projects"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;${toc}&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="-daughter"&gt;🧒 &lt;strong&gt;Daughter&amp;rsquo;s Political Grooming&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-daughter"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strategic plan to groom daughter for Prime Ministerial role (possibly youngest ever).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="-technical-skills--tools"&gt;🔧 &lt;strong&gt;Technical Skills &amp;amp; Tools&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-technical-skills--tools"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Android Development&lt;/strong&gt;: Beginner stage.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WSL (Windows Subsystem for Linux)&lt;/strong&gt;: Actively using it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marp&lt;/strong&gt;: Planning to master the Markdown Presentation Ecosystem.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working in &lt;strong&gt;WSL (Windows Subsystem for Linux)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building minimalist PDF templates for social media content (LinkedIn, Instagram, Medium, Substack)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="-creative-projects"&gt;🎥 &lt;strong&gt;Creative Projects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-creative-projects"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Post-Apocalyptic Series&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Title: &lt;em&gt;the Last Bastard Standing&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Includes dark, philosophical monologues, survivor journal entries, and themes of success/failure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fallout-style visuals, philosophical themes, survival reflections.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Voiceover style: Deep, gritty, female, Indian-British accent, age ~30s, with thunderstorm background.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visual Influencer Project&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Character: &lt;em&gt;Xandra Amgine Thorian&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Setting: Ultra-realistic, cinematic corporate power scenes (e.g. boardroom, top-floor executive suite).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Themes: Control, power, duality, aesthetic noir-futurist styling.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: Parked for future.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Letters to Daughter&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;16 heartfelt, strategic/philosophical letters from Xandra Amgine Thorian to her daughter before her 16th birthday.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fiction &amp;amp; Non-Fiction Books (Planned):&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fiction book: theme and title TBD.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Non-fiction book: theme and title TBD.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="-strategic-manifestos--blueprints"&gt;🧭 &lt;strong&gt;Strategic Manifestos &amp;amp; Blueprints&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-strategic-manifestos--blueprints"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Black-Paper Blueprint: India’s World Dominance&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;India’s World Dominance&lt;/em&gt; – long-term strategic vision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A 100+ page strategic document doubling as a political pitch for your daughter&amp;rsquo;s career.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Themes: Geopolitical dominance, future vision, policy, power plays.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manifesto of the Self-Governed Bastard&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slide-based manifesto targeting complacent leaders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each slide includes a ~500-word spoken script.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tone: Bold, provocative, no-bullshit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LinkedIn Newsletter Series&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Custom title and author voice, portraying you as a transformative leader and strategic thinker.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="-design--visual-assets"&gt;🖼️ &lt;strong&gt;Design &amp;amp; Visual Assets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-design--visual-assets"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One-Pagers / PDF Presentations&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Style: Simple, effective templates with minimal colours.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assets: Hex colours, font pairings, SVG icons.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Platforms: LinkedIn, Instagram, Medium, Substack.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="-character-development"&gt;📖 &lt;strong&gt;Character Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-character-development"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xandra Amgine Thorian&lt;/strong&gt;:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Character Codex includes 32 fictional and 32 real characters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excludes Jessica Pearson and Shaheen Bagh grandmothers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Core Trait: Embodiment of stylish duality — a bikini in the boardroom, a suit on the beach.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xandra Amgine Thorian:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dual-persona character: powerful, stylish, philosophical, unapologetic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visual themes: boardroom in chaos, noir aesthetics, commanding presence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Codex Project:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;32 fictional + 32 real characters influencing Xandra&amp;rsquo;s personality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lisbeth Salander retained, Jessica Pearson &amp;amp; Shaheen Bagh grandmothers excluded.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="-media--storytelling-initiatives"&gt;📽️ &lt;strong&gt;Media &amp;amp; Storytelling Initiatives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-media--storytelling-initiatives"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Voiceover Preferences:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep, gritty Indian-British female voice; thunder in the background.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monologue delivery tone: calm, broken, philosophical.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Studio Vision:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Media studio for audiobooks, films, voiceovers, power narratives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visual Projects:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;NightCafe visuals, hyperrealistic 8K DSLR-style for Xandra in symbolic settings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="-business-plans-in-progress"&gt;📈 &lt;strong&gt;Business Plans (In Progress)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-business-plans-in-progress"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Algorithmic Trading (Derivatives)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marketing &amp;amp; Data Science (Strategy, Branding, Entrepreneurship)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thought &amp;amp; Transformation Consultancy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Virtual Influencer Studio (Xandra-centric brand)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="-upcoming-podcast--events"&gt;🎙️ &lt;strong&gt;Upcoming Podcast &amp;amp; Events&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-upcoming-podcast--events"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Podcast:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Topics: strategy, power, transformation, absurdity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Style: philosophical, witty, sharp.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thought Summit (Planned):&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Annual event: for mavericks, reformers, and big thinkers to reshape the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="-educational-initiatives"&gt;🎓 &lt;strong&gt;Educational Initiatives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-educational-initiatives"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Online Academy (Planned):&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Focus: strategic thinking, storytelling, data-led leadership, self-governance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id="-skills-to-master"&gt;🧑‍🎨 &lt;strong&gt;Skills to Master&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="anchor" href="#-skills-to-master"&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional photography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional drumming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Android development (beginner)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marp (Markdown Presentation Ecosystem)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>