<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Prompts :: Modnar Musings</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/theprompts~00/index.html</link><description>Prompt + Index Femme Fatale [[Prompt + Two Females#Prompt + Two Females in an Intimate Scene]] [[Prompt + Urban Female#Prompt + Urban Female in a Rural Setting]] [[Prompt + Pigment and Purpose#Prompt + Pigment and Purpose]] [[Prompt + Bikini Season#Prompt + Bikini Season]] [[Prompt + Light Female#Prompt + Light Female]] [[Prompt + Lara Croft#Prompt + Lara Croft]] [[Prompt + Activist#Prompt + Activist]] [[Prompt + Herbal Woman#Prompt + Herbal Woman]] [[Prompt + The Black Cats#Prompt + The Black Cats]] [[Prompt + Sunlight#Prompt + Sunlight]] The Images from the Prompts My Image</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 06:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/theprompts~00/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Prompt</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/theprompts~00/prompt-+-prompt/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 06:00:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/theprompts~00/prompt-+-prompt/index.html</guid><description>STYLE: “In style of Moebius + Hayao Miyazaki + Hajime Sorayama, where Moebius’ ethereal world building infuses surreal elevation and vastness, Miyazaki’s mechanical whimsy and steampunk architecture enhance the fantasy of the floating city, and Sorayama’s glossy, sensual precision sharpens the figure’s futuristic design. The fusion should manifest as a cinematic, dreamlike steampunk fantasy with hyper-detailed costume and architecture.”
SUBJECT: “A confident woman in an intricate steampunk bodysuit adorned with gears, straps, and brass elements, standing on a sky-high balcony, gazing out over a floating city. Her long hair flows gently in the breeze as she grips the railing, exuding both strength and elegance.”</description></item><item><title>Template + Prompt</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/theprompts~00/prompt-+-template/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/theprompts~00/prompt-+-template/index.html</guid><description>Template + Prompt Prompt~01 Subject: A woman in her early twenties with short, fluffy, and ruffled hairs. She is an endowed and athletic woman. She is wearing a bright red bikini with red stilettos and a yellow scarf. A simple necklace with a diamond pendant resting just above her breasts. She is wearing hanging earrings. She has tattoos on her arms and thighs. She is smiling confidently with amusement. She is captured from head to toe.</description></item><item><title>The Activist Woman</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/theprompts~00/activist/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/theprompts~00/activist/index.html</guid><description>#NightCafe
Prompt + Activist Activist movement banner that says my body his choice.</description></item><item><title>The Bikini Woman</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/theprompts~00/bikini/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/theprompts~00/bikini/index.html</guid><description>Prompt + Bikini Season 35 year old woman, fitness model getting fit to return to the spotlight, 12 pounds overweight, slightly toned physique, taut supple tanned skin, inverted triangle body shape, long glamorous legs, e cup chest, sandy brown hair, plump lips intense brown eyes Masterpiece, Best Quality, flat, Manga Scan, Anime, cinematic lighting, drawn Art, by Studio Trigger, clip studio paint, Anime Wallpaper, Deep Color, Cel-Shaded.</description></item><item><title>The Herbal Woman</title><link>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/theprompts~00/herbal/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://enemyatgates.github.io/ModnarMusings/theprompts~00/herbal/index.html</guid><description>Prompt + Herbal Woman STYLE: “In style of modern cottage core aesthetics blended with soft natural lighting and vintage charm, where warm, earthy tones, handcrafted details, and nostalgic textures create an idealized, serene domestic moment. The fusion should manifest as a gentle, lived-in atmosphere with subtle sensual realism, evoking quiet presence, warmth, and authenticity.” SUBJECT: “An endowed young woman in 3/4 profile making a salad at a rustic wooden kitchen counter, wearing a fitted, vintage teal dress with large buttons and short sleeves. The fabric rests softly against her figure, showing she is unsupported under her dress, adding a subtle natural realism to the scene. She turns her head toward the viewer, making direct eye contact with a warm and open expression. Her long, curly hair frames her face and catches the soft ambient light.” SETTING: “A cosy cottage kitchen, warmly lit with soft golden tones. Background elements include open shelves with ceramics, stacked bowls, drying herbs, and lived-in clutter. The overall setting feels peaceful and personal, reflecting a quiet, slow-living moment in a storybook countryside home.”</description></item></channel></rss>